<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Big Sky Strong</string>
    <string name="nutritionProgram1Description" formatted="false">
            In this program, you are most likely trying to loose weight and
        gain some muscle while you are at it. There are many different approaches you can take to loose weight, but the important
        thing is that you commit to whatever nutrition change you choose. The core concept in this plan is to be consuming less
        calories than you are outputing. Having a calorie counter is key for this nutrition lifestyle and program. You need to be
        focused on eating 200-400 calories less than your basal metabolic rate which you can find by clicking Here. I would start you
        nutrition change with just trying to eat less than your bmr while maintaining a 30% protein, 30% fat, 40% carbohydrate macro-
        nutrient profile. If you are able to eat consistently under your bmr while having enough energy to continue your life and fitn
        ess endeavors, then this is the best option for you. If you are having trouble achieving this, then there are a couple of
        different nutrition styles that you might be able to try out.
            One of the different styles you may have success with is called Keto Dieting. This is essentially an attempt to convert your body from
        using carbohydrates as fuel to using fat or lipids as fuel. This method is difficult if your lifestyle is dependent on your
        energy. The conquest to become "keto adapted" takes a toll on your energy levels. The macro profile for this type of diet is
        something like 70-75% fats, 20-25% protein, and less than 5% carbohytrates. This may sound like it may be counter intuitive, but the
        research has shown that, once keto adapted, the body eats away body fat for energy instead of just waiting for the next large
        carbohydrate splurge. I encourage you to do your own research into this method. I will say that I did have fairly significant
        success with this diet. I lost 15lbs and gained 5lbs of lean muscle over the course of 5 months. One big mistake that people
        make is consuming large amounts of protein. This will be counter productive to the process because excess protein is stored
        very similar to carbohydrates, as glycogen in the cells instead of fat. In consuming most of your calories from fat, the goal
        is that you will begin to feel more satiated for a longer period of time without having to eat and have a longer span of
        energy after each meal. The final important guideline is to eat healthy fats. This can be anything from coconut oil to
        sunflower oil, but it is imperitive that you stay as far as you can away from trans fats!
            Another style is a method called fasting. This nutrition lifestyle can take many forms. There are several articles talking
        about the different types, which I again urge you to research. This method does not require you to change your macros, but simply
        limits the time in which you are allowed to eat. One of the types requires you to eat your normal macros and calorie deficit
        for five days followed by two days of significantly reduced caloric intake. This would look something like Monday through
        Friday eat 1600-1800 calories and then Saturday through Sunday eat around 600 calories. I have not personally tried this
        method, so I do not know if it would work for me particularly. Yet, there are several documented accounts of this type of
        fasting making significant differences in many lives. The type of fasting that I have personally tried is called intermittent
        fasting. Intermittent fasting is when you have a fasting time window and an eating time window every day. This would look
        something like fasting from 8pm to noon the next day, then eating from noon to 8pm. That method is called the 16:8 method.
        But, you could also try 15:9 and even 14:10 in order to get accustomed to fasting and then steadily increasing your fasting
        time while decreasing your eating window. In my experience, this was very difficult for me due to my work and school
        schedules. My lifestyle requires that I have energy in the ealy hours of the morning and without eating, it was just not
        possible for me. But, this does not mean that it has not worked for others who also have hectic lives.
            There are other tricks (or methods) out there for those people (myself included) that have trouble eating a caloric deficit.
        I believe that the most important thing is just trying these methods out. Everyone is different so different weight loss
        methods are going to help people and others are not going to be beneficial. It is also important that you do not feel like
        you have failed if you tried one of the methods and it did not work for you. Failure is a part of life and (as I am sure you
        already know) it is what you learn about yourself from attempting these methods that is true success. Ergo, do not become
        discouraged, but instead become motivated to find the method that works for you!
    </string>
    <string name="aboutMe">
            The first thing you should know about me is that I have many, many issues. First, I am moderately allergic to lactose
        and grass, but I am also severely allergic to chlorine. I suffer from something called Eczema which is kind of like a really
        itchy rash. This is also exaggerated by sweat and harsh chemicals in clothing. I have been made fun of since I first started
        school for being fat and having rashes all over my skin. As, you can imagine this has led me to suffer greatly in the gym and
        when I start to sweat when working out. I start to get rashes all over my body. For the longest time I have had to deal with
        people always looking at me wierd in the gym for sweating so much and having all these rashes, but the truth is that you just
        have to learn to ignore them. When you go to the gym, you are going to better yourself and anyone that is looking at you and
        judging you negatively for putting in an effort should be ashamed of themselves. I still catch myself thinking about how
        other people view me, but then I just have to keep my mind on the exercise, crank up the music, and rock the workout.
    </string>

    <string name="OrgainProteinPowderReviewPros">
            I enjoy this protein powder because it tastes really great in smothies but I would not recoomend it in just water.
        This protein powder gets its protein source from mainly plant-based sources, so this is perfect for me since I am lactose
        intollerant.
    </string>
    <string name="OrgainProteinPowderReviewCons">
            Since this is a plant based protein, it is a little bit grainy, but not nearly as grainy as the protein powders from
        other companies like vega. Yet, if you are not lactose intollerant, I would reccomend using a protein powder that gets its
        protein from sources like whey or milk protein. This is because that protein will be more easily absorbed by your muscles
        and it is often the cheapest source of protein
    </string>

    <string name="CnsixReviewPros">
            This is my creatine that I really enjoy! It is only about 3g, but I think it is helping me gain lean muscle. This product
        is not really for those who really want to bulk, but for those who are looking to make some lean gains.
    </string>
    <string name="CnsixReviewCons">
            There are not really any cons again other than you have to be patient in order to see the results, and you have to be
        consistent in using the product (every day).
    </string>

    <string name="HemoShockReviewPros">
            The pros for this one is that (at least for me) I only need to take about a half a scoop of this pre-workout to get
        me going. Therefore it lasts me over two months. Also, the taste is alright, and I take this preworkout, my creatine,
        and nitric oxide all at the same time (around 15-20 minutes before working out). This has a medium amount of caffeine in it
        so it doesn\'t freak you out, but it is enough to get you focused.
    </string>
    <string name="HemoShockReviewCons">
            The cons are probably the fact that it has caffeine in it, so it is important to rotate this pre-workout with other
        non-stimulant pre-workouts.
    </string>




//==================================================ARMS=====================================================================

    <string name="P1L1">
        Backsquat, 5 sets of (20,18,16,14,12)
    </string>
    <string name="P1L2">
        Leg Extensions Superset With Wall Sit, 4 sets of 20 extensions to a 60 second wall sit
    </string>
    <string name="P1L3">
        Barbell Straight Leg Deadlift Superset Calf Raise
        4 sets of 10-15 reps
    </string>
    <string name="P1L4">
        Lying Leg Curl Superset Jump Rope
        3 sets of (20/100, 20/100, 20/100)
    </string>

//=========================================================SHOULDERS============================================================

    <string name="P1S1">
        Barbell Shoulder Press 4 sets of 10 reps
    </string>
    <string name="P1S2">
        Lateral DB Raises, 5 sets of (30, 25, 20, 15, drop: 10/10/15)
    </string>
    <string name="P1S3">
        Rear Delt Cable Flys, 4 sets of (35, 25, 15, 10)
    </string>
    <string name="P1S4">
        Seated Face Pulls Superset with Low to High Row, 4 sets of (15/15, 15/15, 15/15, 15/15)
    </string>
    <string name="P1S5">
        Dumbell Front Raise, Palm Up Lateral Hold, Palm Down Lower Front Raise
        3 sets of 10 reps
    </string>



    //=====================================================ARMS=============================================================

    <string name="P1A1">
    Tricep Pushdown Random Selection, 10 sets of 10 reps (partner randomly decides weight for each set)
    </string>
    <string name="P1A2">
        Standing Cable Bicep Curl, 4 sets of (20, 18, 16, 12)
    </string>
    <string name="P1A3">
EZ Bar Flat Bench Skullcrusher Superset With Close Grip Flat Bench Press, 5 sets of (20, 18, 16, 14, 12)
    </string>
    <string name="P1A4">
Overhead Rope Extensions Super Set With Standing Rope Curls, 4 sets of (30/25, 25/20, 20/15, 15/10)
    </string>
    <string name="P1A5">
Close Grip Cable Tricep Pushdown Superset With Wide Grip Reverse Tricep Cable Pulldown, 4 sets of (20/20, 20/20, 20/20, 20/20)
    </string>

    <string name="P2A1">
        Machine Curl: 4 X 20,20,15,10
    </string>
    <string name="P2A2">
        Rope Tricep Pulldown: 5 X 12 - 15
    </string>
    <string name="P2A3">
        Incline DB Curl: 4 X 12 - 15
    </string>
    <string name="P2A4">
        Bench DB Skull Crusher: 3 X 15,15,12
    </string>
    <string name="P2A5">
        Reverse Grip Cable Tricep Pulldown: 4 X 20,15,15,12
    </string>
    <string name="P2A6">
        Superset:
            Bicep BB Curl: 3 X 12
            Diamond Pushup: 3 X 12
    </string>
    <string name="P2A7">
        Seated DB Curl: 3 X 12 - 15
    </string>
    <string name="P2A8">
        Overhead Cable Tricep Extensions: 3 X 12 - 15
    </string>

    //===================================CHEST==============================================================

    <string name="P1C1">
    Superset: Cable Crossover to Pushups, 5 sets of (20/20, 18/18, 16/16, 14/14, 12/12)
    </string>
    <string name="P1C2">
          Machine Chest Press, 4 sets of (20,20,20,20)
    </string>
    <string name="P1C3">
Superset: Smith Machine Incline Press to Dumbell Incline Fly, 4 sets of (20/15, 16/15, 12/15, 8/15)
    </string>
    <string name="P1C4">
Superset: Low-High Cable Chest Fly to Machine Pec Flys, 4 sets of (10/20, 10/20, 10/20, 10/20), 1 set of drop set for each exercise
    </string>
    <string name="P1C5">
DB Flat Bench Fly Superset With DB Flat Bench Press, 4 sets of (10/15, 10/15, 10/15, 10/15)
    </string>



    /*-----------------------Craig Capurso Chest Workout-----------------------------------------*/

    <string name="P2C1">
        Reverse Grip Decline Bench Press
        Warmup, 10 X 3, 30 second rest
    </string>
    <string name="P2C2">
        Alternate DB Press, neutral grip
        6 X 5, 30 second rest
    </string>
    <string name="P2C3">
        Seated Horizontal Hammer Press on Machine
        5 X 6, 30 second rest
    </string>
    <string name="P2C4">
        Seated Machine Fly
        3 X 10, 30 second rest
    </string>
    <string name="P2C5">
        Svend Press
        2 X 15, 30 second rest
    </string>
    <string name="P2C6">
        Single Arm Top Cable Fly
        1 set ascending reps (2,4,6,8,10)
    </string>
    <string name="P2C7">
        Jump Rope
        10 X 20 second work X 10 second rest
    </string>
    <string name="P2C8">
        Stair Climber
        20 minutes
    </string>

    //=========================================BACK===========================================

    <string name="P1B1">
    Pullups: 4 sets of 10 reps
    80-120 sec. rest
    </string>
    <string name="P1B2">
        Single Arm Dumbbell Row Superset Dumbbell Reverse Fly:
 		4 sets, 10 reps
 		80-120 sec rest
    </string>
    <string name="P1B3">
        Superset: Lat Pulldown to Straight Arm Pulldown, 5 sets of (20/20, 18/18, 16/16, 14/14, 12/12)
    </string>
    <string name="P1B4">
        T-Bar Close-Grip Row Superset Lower Back Hyperextensions
        4 sets of (15,12,10,8)
    </string>

    /*--------------------------------Physiques of Greatness Back----------------------------------------*/

    <string name="P2B1">
        Superset:
            DB Pullover
            Bodyweight Pullups
    </string>

    <string name="P2B2">
        Reverse Straight Arm Cable Pulldown
    </string>

    <string name="P2B3">
        Wide Grip Lat Pulldown
    </string>

    <string name="P2B4">
        V-Grip Lat Pulldown
    </string>

    <string name="P2B5">
        Close Grip T-Bar Row
    </string>

    <string name="P2B6">
        Single Arm Cable Rows
    </string>

    <string name="P2B7">
        Superset:
            Wide Grip Cable Row
            DB Row
    </string>

    <string name="P2B8">
        Standing Bicep Cable Curl
    </string>

    <string name="P2B9">
        Reverse Grip Cable Curl
    </string>

    <string name="fatsecretAPIKey">8456c1a777c2481ca27386007fc229c9d</string>
    <string name="fatSecretAPISharedSecret">d49e8faf934d4d85ac883b016c157ffe</string>

</resources>
